wedmantra.com 2015-06-07

# wedmantra.com -Privacy Policy

##  privacy policy

This Privacy policy sets out how Wedmantra uses & protects any information that you give to us when you visit the Website.

Wedmantra is committed to ensure user privacy is protected. We ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Wedmantra may change its privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are satisfied with the privacy policy. This policy is effective from 31st July 2014.

**What information we collect?**

  1. Name
  2. Contact information including email address and postal code
  3. Demographic information, preferences and interests
  4. Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather?**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better services, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  1. Internal record keeping.
  2. Improve our products and services and customize the website according to your interests.
  3. Periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information, which we think would be interesting to you.
  4. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by phone, fax or mail.

**Security**

We are committed to ensure that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information what we collect online.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information, which you provide while visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties, which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
You may request details of personal information, which we hold about you under the Information Technology Act 2000.   
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at :  
Company Name: Wedmantra,  
5th Floor, "Jubilee Square," Road No. 36, Jubilee Hills, Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh 500033  
Phone Nos :  
Dialling from India : 1860-200-4444  
Dialling from outside India : (00) 91 088 86 677733  
E-Mail ID :   
For Technnical Support : [support@wedmantra.com](mailto:support@wedmantra.com)  
For Customer Support : [enquiries@wedmantra.com](mailto:enquiries@wedmantra.com), [info@wedmantra.com](mailto:info@wedmantra.com)
